safesearch.net 2014-07-02

# Search

## Privacy Policy

AVSoftware, LLC ("AVSoftware") takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about AVSoftware's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how AVSoftware receives, collects and uses information in connection with their website located at SafeSearch.net and software provided on the SafeSearch.net website (the website and software collectively referred to herein as "Site").

### Collection and Use of Information

AVSoftware does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as names, e-mail, age, gender, address, telephone numbers, login names and passwords or other self-identifying information ("Personal Information"). AVSoftware may request that a user provide an e-mail address if such user wishes to be contacted regarding any offers, updates, newsletters and service related announcements. If a user provides an e-mail address to AVSoftware, such user authorizes AVSoftware to send user communications.

AVSoftware may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are at AVSoftware's Site. Cookies may be used to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout and for other customer service purposes. AVSoftware's use of cookies is in no way linked to any Personal Information.

AVSoftware may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits. AVSoftware collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. AVSoftware will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of its users.

### AVSoftware and Disclosure of Information

AVSoftware does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties. AVSoftware may disclose your Personal Information if AVSoftware believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on AVSoftware; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of AVSoftware (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of AVSoftware services or members of the public.

### Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. We operate our website in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We never knowingly collect or maintain information at or on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 13. Visitors younger than 13 years of age may NOT use the AVSoftware website and software and must LEAVE immediately.

### Security

AVSoftware takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although AVSoftware cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, AVSoftware has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. Personal Information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.

### Business Transitions

In the event that AVSoftware goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. AVSoftware will post a notice on this website of any such change in ownership or control of the Personal Information AVSoftware may have prior to such transfer.

### Changes to Policy

From time to time, AVSoftware may revise this Policy. AVSoftware will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information AVSoftware collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed.
